[{"answer": "You mean in a real Fight Fight", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Buffer zone", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Oh yeah that's shocking, but sounds ..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oh, hey my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " She called my friend last night", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "How do you know", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Wha'd you do that for", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Well that was a really stupid thing! You know what's going to happen now", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Ah, so, ah, flower shows and, shopping for pretty bows, and then back to her place, strip down to bra and panties for a tickle fight?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yes, I do.", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Who? Who is my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What pool guy", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, the apartment elevators are always slower than the offices, because you don't have to be home on time.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Hey. So, ah, my friend this is my friend my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "All right.  Moving subway cars blur by, then inside the subway car where my friend sits next to my frien", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "All right my friend, I'm going to get going.", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You know, uh, she has no female friends! You know that, don't cha? Something strange about a woman who's friends are all men", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You talked all about that", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well it's a little strange. You going to start to talk like my friend from now on", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "We'd all go to movie on Friday", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "my friend and welcome to Movie phone. Brought to you by the that place and Hot 97. Coming to theaters this Friday ... my friend, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Tell me about it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You're meeting my friend for lunch at the coffee shop", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Hey", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Huh", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pool-Guy.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You go", "qsentId": 30}]